LINSY JOYNER

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

🖾 linsy.joyner@gmail.com 📞 (772) 480-2735 👖 linkedin.com/in/linsydeanna 🔘 github.com/linsydeanna



ABOUT ME

I am a front end web developer with a passion for creating work of excellence. After gaining five years of valuable experience in employee and program management, I am transitioning into a best-fit career in tech where I am utilizing my creativity and problem-solving skills. My goal is to be a leader in my field by speaking at meetups and events and focusing on how to write clean and efficient code.

SKILLS

JavaScript

React

HTML

CSS

Git & Github

JQuery

Responsive Web Design

APIs

Firebase

Command Line

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Premiere

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE Front End Engineering The Iron Yard 2016

MASTER'S DEGREE Counseling Psychology Palm Beach Atlantic University 2014 - 2015

BACHELOR'S DEGREE Sports and Fitness University of Central Florida 2007 - 2010

EXPERIENCE

THE IRON YARD Front End Engineering Student 7/2016 - 10/2016

At The Iron Yard, I participated in a 12-week coding bootcamp in which I learned how to problem solve using JavaScript for both individual and team projects. After a 3-week long final project, I graduated with a strong core front end programming skillset. Key accomplishments from this experience include:

- studying and implementing JavaScript concepts such as types, functions, objects, scope, closures, constructors, prototypes and more
- building over 35 projects including a full web application using Firebase
- learning how to build an application with React
- creating user-friendly and responsive layouts for mobile and tablet views
- incorporating additional tools such as CSS preprocessors, JavaScript libraries, and testing frameworks

THE CHRIST SCHOOL **REACH and Summer in the City Coordinator** 10/2011 - Present

At The Christ School, I interviewed and hired, trained, and led a team of 12-20 employees in the after-school and summer programs. I communicated with families regarding program contracts, monitored the safety and security of the student environment, and handled student and employee issues. Key accomplishments from this experience include:

- increasing program registration and revenue
- expanding summer program offerings
- transitioning student check-in and check-out to an electronic system for better campus security
- introducing and implementing tools and procedures for enhanced team communication
- working with team leadership to better communicate program branding and mission statements to school families